Guide to the Office of the President Records, Sarah Gibson Blanding Files, 1911-1977 (bulk 1946-1964)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series VIII. Additions, 1943-1977
  - Correspondence: Wislocki, Florence (Clothier) to Virginia Smith, regarding Sarah Gibson Blanding, 1977 Aug 29 (Folder 26.40)
  - "The Study of Development Planning in Women's Colleges - Profiles of Participating Colleges and Bibliography of Development Materials,", 1962 Oct 5-6 (Folder 26.41)
  - "The Study of Development Planning in Women's Colleges - Statements by Participating Colleges,", 1962 Oct 5-6 (Folder 26.42)